Arriv
IQ
How It Works
Features
Pricing
Coverage
Start Free Trial
🚶 Passengers Walking to Arrivals
LIVE MONITORING
PASSENGERS
Walking to Arrivals
Terminal corridor · 3 min ETA
DRIVER JAMES
Name Board Ready
AB12 CDE · Parked outside
BUILT FOR UK CHAUFFEUR & MEET & GREET COMPANIES
Stop guessing when
your customer lands.
ArrivIQ tells your driver.
Your driver gets a WhatsApp alert automatically — 45 minutes before every return flight lands. No more manually checking FlightAware. No more missed pickups. No more angry customers waiting outside arrivals.

✓
Works for return pickups
✓
Works for car drop-offs
✓
Instant alerts for delays & diversions
✓
All 40+ UK airports covered
See Pricing — 30 Day Free Trial
Book a Free Demo ›
40+
UK airports covered
45 min
Before landing — driver alerted
3
Live flight data sources
£0
Staff time checking flights
24/7
Monitoring — no days off
HOW IT WORKS
Set it up once.
It works forever after that.
No software to install. No training needed. Your team just saves the flight number at booking time — ArrivIQ does everything else from that moment onwards.
01
Customer gives flight number

When a customer books, they give their flight number. Your team links it to the car registration. That's it — nothing else to do.
›
02
ArrivIQ watches the flight

From that moment, ArrivIQ tracks the flight every 5 minutes using 3 live data sources. Your team don't need to check anything manually.
›
03
System decides when to alert

ArrivIQ works out the perfect moment to send the alert — 45 minutes before landing. If the flight is delayed or diverted, it alerts the driver straight away.
›
04
Driver gets a WhatsApp

The driver receives a WhatsApp message with the flight status, terminal, landing time, passenger name and car reg — everything they need in one message.
WHAT ARRIVIQ DOES FOR YOU
Stop paying staff to
watch flight boards.
Every UK airport covered
Heathrow, Gatwick, Manchester, Edinburgh and all 40+ UK airports. Your drivers get alerts no matter which airport the customer flies into — from day one, no setup needed.
Never misses a flight change
If a flight is delayed, diverted or cancelled, your driver gets an instant WhatsApp — not a notification 3 hours later. We check 3 live data sources every 5 minutes so nothing slips through.
Works for drop-offs too
Not just return pickups. When a customer drops their car before flying out, ArrivIQ tracks their outbound flight and alerts your team at the right time — no more staff standing around waiting.
Driver gets everything in one message
Flight status, terminal, landing time, passenger name, car registration — all in a single WhatsApp. No back-and-forth calls. No confusion. Just one clear message and the driver knows exactly what to do.
Full record of every alert sent
Every WhatsApp logged with exact timestamp, flight status and confirmation it was delivered. Useful if a customer ever disputes a missed pickup — you have proof of exactly what happened.
Fits around how you already work
No need to change your booking system. ArrivIQ works alongside whatever software you use today. Larger operators can connect via our full API or use white-label branding under their own name.
LIVE FLIGHT INTELLIGENCE
Your driver knows what's happening
before it happens.
Every possible flight event — handled automatically. Your team never need to check a single thing.
✅
ON TIME
45-min alert sent
Flight is on schedule. Driver gets terminal, gate and exact landing time — 45 minutes before touchdown.
WhatsApp sent:
"BA0245 landing in 45 mins. LHR T5. John Smith. AB12 CDE."
⏳
DELAYED
Instant new ETA
Flight pushed back. Driver is notified immediately with the new landing time so they don't leave too early.
WhatsApp sent:
"BA0245 now delayed. New ETA 18:45. Please adjust pickup time."
🔀
DIVERTED
Different airport alert
Flight landing somewhere else. Driver gets the new airport immediately — before the passenger even lands.
WhatsApp sent:
"URGENT — BA0245 diverted to Gatwick LGW. Contact passenger."
❌
CANCELLED
Booking flagged instantly
Flight cancelled. Driver and office both notified immediately. No wasted trip. No angry customer waiting.
WhatsApp sent:
"BA0245 cancelled. Do not travel to airport. Contact John Smith."
ArrivIQ monitors every flight every 5 minutes, 24 hours a day, 7 days a week
✓ No app for drivers
✓ No training needed
✓ Just WhatsApp
WHAT THE DRIVER RECEIVES
One WhatsApp.
Everything they need.
AI
ArrivIQ
WhatsApp · Just now
✈️ 45 Min Notice — BA0245

Hi James,

Flight BA0245 is on schedule, landing in ~45 minutes.

📍 Airport: Heathrow (LHR) — T5
🕐 ETA: 14:15 UTC
👤 Passenger: John Smith
🚗 Car Reg: AB12 CDE

Please proceed to arrivals. Safe driving! 🙏
Delivered ✓✓
✅
On Time — 45-min alert
Sent exactly 45 minutes before landing. Driver gets terminal, ETA, passenger name and car reg in one message.
⏳
Flight Delayed
Immediate alert with new ETA the moment a delay is confirmed. Driver rescheduled automatically.
🔀
Flight Diverted
Urgent alert with new airport. Driver prompted to update pickup location and contact passenger.
❌
Flight Cancelled
Immediate alert. Booking flagged and driver prompted to contact passenger directly.
PRICING
Built for real fleet sizes.
No surprises.
Priced per vehicle, not per journey — costs stay flat even on your busiest days. 30-day free trial on all plans.

A company doing 30 return pickups a day spends ~£500–£650/month in coordinator time watching flight boards. ArrivIQ pays for itself within the first week.

Monthly
Annual
STARTER
£149 /month
🎁 30-day free trial included
Sole traders & small operators.
✦
Up to 15 vehicles
✦
All 40+ UK airports
✦
WhatsApp driver alerts
✦
Email support
✦
Flight API monitoring
Start Free Trial →
MOST POPULAR
GROWTH
£299 /month
🎁 30-day free trial included
Best for 30+ return pickups per day.
✦
Up to 40 vehicles
✦
Priority API access
✦
Phone & chat support
✦
Analytics dashboard
✦
Multi-driver alerts
Start Free Trial →
PRO
£499 /month
🎁 30-day free trial included
Multi-airport established operators.
✦
Up to 80 vehicles
✦
Dedicated account manager
✦
SLA guarantee
✦
Custom WhatsApp templates
✦
Bulk booking import
Start Free Trial →
ENTERPRISE
£799 /month
🎁 30-day free trial included
White-label & API for large fleets.
✦
Unlimited vehicles
✦
Full REST API access
✦
White-label branding
✦
Custom integration
✦
Priority onboarding
Start Free Trial →
How to choose your plan

Starter
Sole traders, 1–2 drivers, up to 15 vehicles. Perfect to start.
Growth
30+ pickups/day, 20–40 vehicles. Most popular for Heathrow operators.
Pro
Multi-airport fleets up to 80 vehicles with a dedicated account manager.
Enterprise
Unlimited vehicles, white-label branding, full REST API access.
AIRPORT COVERAGE
Every UK airport. From day one.
ArrivIQ covers all IATA-coded UK airports. Major hubs in teal.
Heathrow · LHR
Gatwick · LGW
Manchester · MAN
Stansted · STN
Luton · LTN
Edinburgh · EDI
Birmingham · BHX
Glasgow · GLA
Bristol · BRS
London City · LCY
Newcastle · NCL
Leeds Bradford · LBA
Liverpool · LPL
East Midlands · EMA
Belfast · BFS
Aberdeen · ABZ
Cardiff · CWL
Southampton · SOU
+ All Others
Your drivers should never
be waiting at the wrong time.
Join UK chauffeur and meet & greet companies using ArrivIQ. Try it free for 30 days — no card charged, no commitment, cancel any time.

Start Free Trial — No Card Now
Book a Demo
Arriv
IQ
© 2026 ArrivIQ Ltd · All rights reserved · Registered in England & Wales
Privacy
Terms
Contact
API Docs
